A Guide to the University of Virginia Hospital Executive Director's Office (HEDO) Collection
Claude Moore Health Sciences Library
- CEREBRAL PALSY CLINIC CORRESPONDENCE 1953 - 1955, TL, TLS (2) (Box-folder 10:024)
- CEREBRAL PALSY CLINIC 1956 - 1957, TL, TLS (2) (Box-folder 10:025)
- CEREBRAL PALSY CLINIC 1958 - 1967, TL, TLS (2) (Box-folder 10:026)
- MINUTES FROM THE BUDGET COMMITTEE OF THE CEREBRAL PALSY CLINIC July 7, 1955, TMs (Box-folder 10:027)
- REPORT OF CURRENT OPERATIONS, CEREBRAL PALSY CLINIC 1955 - 1956, TMs (Box-folder 10:028)
- REPORT OF CURRENT OPERATIONS, CEREBRAL PALSY CLINIC 1957 - 1958, TMs (Box-folder 10:029)
- REPORT OF CURRENT OPERATIONS, CEREBRAL PALSY CLINIC 1959 - 1967, TMs (Box-folder 10:030)
- STERILIZATION POLICY CORRESPONDENCE 1962 - 1979, TL (2), TLS (2), TMs (Box-folder 10:031)
- LAWS, BY-LAWS, RULES & REGULATIONS: QUESTIONNAIRES 1969 - 1970, TMs (Box-folder 10:032)
  RE: STERILIZATION & ABORTION POLICY
- UVA MEDICAL CENTER: LARGEST AREA EMPLOYER OF PEOPLE IN LOWER INCOME BRACKETS, THE UNDERPRIVILIGED, THE HANDICAPPED AND THOSE IN MINORITY GROUPS 1969, TMs, AMs (Box-folder 10:033)
  FROM URBAN RENEWAL FILE
- MEDICAL CENTER: SPACE & PROGRAM CRITERIA 1965, TMs (Box-folder 10:034)
- REPORTS ON THE TRAINING PROJECT: UPGRADING UNIVERSITY EMPLOYMENT OPPORTUNITIES 1968 - 1969, TMs (Box-folder 10:035)
- URBAN RENEWAL CORRESPONDENCE AND MISCELLANEOUS MS. 1968 - 1969, TL, TLS, TMs (Box-folder 10:036)
- UVA FACULTY September 1967, TMs (Box-folder 11:001)
- DIETARY DEPT. CORRESPONDENCE 1958 - 1964, TL, TLS (2) (Box-folder 11:002)
- DIETARY DEPT. CORRESPONDENCE 1965 - 1967, TL, TLS (2) (Box-folder 11:003)
- DIETARY DEPT. CORRESPONDENCE 1968 - 1978, TL, TLS (2) (Box-folder 11:004)
- CONFIDENTIAL QUESTIONNAIRE-HOSPITAL FOOD SERVICE, 1966 April 28, 1966, TLS (Box-folder 11:005)
  FROM DIETARY DEPT. FILE
- CAFETERIA CENSUS & REVENUE March - May 1967, Chart (Box-folder 11:006)
  DIETARY DEPT. FILE
- THE DIETARY DIGEST: WEEKLY NEWS SHEET, DEPT. OF DIETARY SERVICE 1968 - 1969, TMs (Box-folder 11:007)
- PATIENT QUESTIONNAIRE RESULTS 1968?, Chart (Box-folder 11:008)
- STUDY OF THE AUTOMATED NOURISHMENT DISPENSIVE SYSTEM FOR PATIENTS AT THE UVA HOSPITAL March 24, 1970, TMs (Box-folder 11:009)
  FROM DIETARY DEPARTMENT FILE
- VARIOUS MENUS AT UVA HOSPITAL 1970, TMs (Box-folder 11:010)
- MENU FOR 2 WEEKS, UVA HOSPITAL November 1970, TL, TMs (Box-folder 11:011)
- UVA HOSPITAL DEPT. OF DIETARY SERVICE: ECONOMIC SUMMARY, 1968-1971 1970, ANS, TMs, TLS (Box-folder 11:012)
- DIETETIC INTERNSHIP APPLICATION September 1970, ANS, TMs, Questionnaire (Box-folder 11:013)
- REPORT OF THE FOOD SERVICE MANAGER ON FOOD PRICE INCREASES & AVAILABILITIES MARCH 1973-AUGUST 1973 1973, TLS, TMs (Box-folder 11:014)
- RELOCATION OF THE BAKERY OPERATION AT UVA HOSPITAL 1974, TMs (Box-folder 11:015)
- PRELIMINARY APPLICATION FOR APPROVAL OF HOSPITAL DIETETIC INTERNSHIP 1970, TMs (Box-folder 11:016)
- SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIALS FOR PRELIMINARY APPLICATION FOR HOSPITAL DIETETIC INTERNSHIP 1970, TLS, TMs (Box-folder 11:017)
- REPORT OF THE UTILISATION OF NURSING SERVICE PERSONNEL AT THE UVA HOSPITAL PHASE II OPERATING ROOM November 1959, TMs (Box-folder 11:018)
- SCHOOL OF NURSING, GRADUATE NURSING PROGRAM CORRESPONDENCE 1968 - 1969, TL, ALS, TLS (Box-folder 11:019)
- SCHOOL OF NURSING, GRADUAT NURSING PROGRAM MISCELLANEOUS 1966 - 1968, Newsclippings, TMs (Box-folder 11:020)
- SCHOOL OF NURSING EDUCATION BUILDING CORRESPONDENCE 1968 - 1972, AL, TL (2), TLS (Box-folder 11:021)
- SCHOOL OF NURSING EDUCATION BUILDING PLANNING COMMITTEE MINUTES AND MEMORANDA 1967, AMs, TMs (Box-folder 11:022)
- SCHOOL OF NURSING EDUCATION BUILDING PLANNING COMMITTEE MEMORANDA & MINUTES 1967, TMs (Box-folder 11:023)
- SCHOOL OF NURSING EDUCATION BUILDING: COST ESTIMATES & CONSTRUCTION DATA REPORTS 1970, TMs (Box-folder 11:024)
- CLINICAL RESEARCH CENTER CORRESPONDENCE 1967 - 1968, TL, TMs, TLS (2) (Box-folder 11:025)
- APPLICATION FOR RESEARCH GRANT: GENERAL CLINICAL RESEARCH CENTER, ADULT-PEDIATRIC, 10 BEDS October 1965, TMs (Box-folder 11:026)
  FROM CLINICAL RESEARCH CENTER FILE
- OUTLINE SPECIFICATION COMMISSION: GENERAL CLINICAL RESEARCH CENTER, ADULT-PEDIATRIC, 10 BEDS December 1, 1965, TMs (Box-folder 11:027)
- OUTLINE SPECIFICATION: GENERAL CLINICAL RESEARCH CENTER, ADULT-PEDIATRIC, 10 BEDS December 1, 1965, TMs (Box-folder 11:028)
- REMARKS BEFORE THE PROGRAM DIRECTORS OF THE SOUTHERN SECTION OF THE AMERICAN FEDERATION FOR CLINICAL RESEARCH January 1967, TLS, TMs (Box-folder 11:029)
- CLINICAL RESEARCH CENTER, UVA HOSPITAL, CHARLOTTESVILLE, VA. October 1967, TLS, TMs (Box-folder 11:030)
- CLINICAL RESEARCH CENTER: PROPOSALS FOR RESEARCH PROJECTS 1968, TMs (Box-folder 11:031)
- CLINICA RESEARCH CENTER, UVA HOSPITAL 1968, TMs (Box-folder 11:032)
- PROPOSED BUDGET FOR CLINICAL RESEARCH CENTER 1968, TMs (Box-folder 11:033)
- TEACHING PLAN FOR RESIDENCEY PROGRAM: DEPT. OF OPHTHAMOLOGY 1970?, TMs, Questionnaire (Box-folder 11:034)
- MEDICAL CLINIC CORRESPONDENCE 1965 - 1974, TL, TLS (Box-folder 12:001)
- CLINICAL STAFF CORRESPONDENCE 1953 - 1966, TL, TLS (2) (Box-folder 12:002)
- CLINICAL STAFF COMMITTEES 1957 - 1970, TMs (Box-folder 12:003)
  LISTS OF COMMITTEES AND THEIR MEMBERS
- CLINICAL STAFF CORRESPONDENCE 1967 - 1978, TL, TLS, TMs (Box-folder 12:004)
- CLINICAL STAFF MINUTES OF REGULAR MONTHLY MEETINGS 1954 - 1956, TMs (Box-folder 12:005)
- CLINICAL STAFF MINUTES 1962 - 1970, TMs, TMsS (Box-folder 12:006)
- STEERING COMMITTEE OF THE CLINICAL STAFF MINUTES 1956 - 1961, TMs (Box-folder 12:007)
- BY-LAWS FOR THE CLINICAL STAFF OF THE UNIVERSITY OF VIRGINIA HOSPITAL 1956, TMs (Box-folder 12:008)
- BY-LAWS, RULES & REGULATIONS OF THE CLINICAL STAFF OF UVA HOSPITAL\ 1966?, TMs (Box-folder 12:009)
- BY-LAWS, RULES & REGULATIONS OF THE CLINICAL STAFF OF UVA HOSPITAL 1970, TMs (Box-folder 12:010)
- BY-LAWS: CHANGES IN STERILIZATION POLICY February 1970, TL, TMs (Box-folder 12:011)
- UNIVERSITY OF VIRGINIA MEDICAL CENTER HOSPITAL DISASTER PLAN March 1970, TL, TMs (Box-folder 12:012)
  FROM CLINICAL STAFF FILE
- PEDIATRIC INTENSIVE CARE UNIT CORRESPNDENCE 1974 - 1975, TL, TLS, TMs (Box-folder 12:013)
- PEDIATRIC INTENSIVE CARE COMMITTEE MINUTES 1974, TMs (Box-folder 12:014)
- PEDIATRIC INTENSIVE CARE UNIT SUMMARIES OF DATA 1973 - 1974, TMs (Box-folder 12:015)
  RE: PATIENT CARE STATISTICS
- PRIMARY CARE CENTER CORRESPONDENCE 1974 - 1978, TL, TLS (2) (Box-folder 12:016)
- PROJECT PROPOSAL FOR PRIMARY CARE CENTER 1973 - 1974, AN, TLS, TMs (Box-folder 12:017)
- CONTRAST BETWEEN UVA & ARCHITECTS COLLABORATIVE February 26, 1974, TDoc, TMs (Box-folder 12:018)
  RE: PRIMARY CARE CENTER
- APPLICANT'S PROGRESS REPORT 1974, Xerox application (Box-folder 12:019)
  RE: PRIMARY CARE CENTER CONSTRUCTION ESTIMATES
- PRIMARY CARE BUILDING COMMITTEE MINUTES 1973 - 1974, TMs (Box-folder 12:020)
- SUMMATION OF SUBCOMMITTEE ON COMMUNICATIONS FOR THE PRIMARY CARE CENTER September 1974, TMs, Floor plans (Box-folder 12:021)
- PRIMARY CARE CENTER COORDINATING COUNCIL MINUTES 1978 - 1979, TLS, TMs (Box-folder 12:022)
- CENTRAL STERILE SUPPLY FILE CORRESPONDENCE 1954 - 1955, TL (Box-folder 12:023)
- CENTRAL STERILE SUPPLY ADVISORY COMMITTEE MINUTES 1954, TMs (Box-folder 12:024)
- BIOMEDICAL ENGINEERING CORRESPONDENCE 1967 - 1978, TL, TLS, TMs (Box-folder 12:025)
- PROPOSAL FOR SUBCONTRACT ON: INTERPLAY OF ENGINEERING WITH BIOLOGY AND MEDICINE December 15, 1967, TL, TMs (Box-folder 12:026)
  FROM BIOMEDICAL ENGINEERING FILE
- RECOMMENDATIONS FOR ESTABLISHING A UVA BIOMEDICAL COMPUTER FACILITY May 1969, TLS, TMs (Box-folder 12:027)
- GRANT APPLICATION FOR PROPOSAL: CARE & EVALUATION OF THE CRITICALLY ILL PATIENT 1969, TMs (Box-folder 12:028)
- ARTIFICIAL KIDNEY AND TRANSPLANTATION CORRESPONDENCE 1964 - 1968, TL, TLS (Box-folder 12:029)
- ARTIFICIAL KIDNEY AND TRANSPLANTATION: MISCELLANEOUS 1966 - 1968, TMs, Pamphlet (Box-folder 12:030)
- COMMONWEALTH COURT CORRESPONDENCE 1964 - 1967, TL, TLS, TMs (Box-folder 12:031)
- COMMONWEALTH COURT CORRESPONDENCE 1968 - 1970, TL, TLS (2) (Box-folder 12:032)
- COMMONWEALTH COURT CORRESPONDENCE 1971 - 1975, TL, TLS (2), TMs (Box-folder 12:033)
- COMMONWEALTH COURT UNIT OPERATING FUND REPORTS 1970 - 1975, TMs (Box-folder 12:034)
- COMMONWEALTH MOTOR COURT, ROUTE 250 WEST, CHARLOTTESVILLE, VIRGINIA December 1964, TLS, TMs (Box-folder 12:035)
  COMMONWEALTH COURT FILE
- SUMMARY OF ACTIONS RELATING TO THE CERTIFICATION OF COMMONWEALTH COURT 1967 - 1968, TL, TLS, TMs (Box-folder 12:036)
- APPLICATION FOR LICENSE RENEWAL: HOSPITALS September 1975, TL (Box-folder 12:037)
  FROM COMMONWEALTH COURT FILE
- COMMONWEALTH COURT: MISCELLANEOUS 1967 - 1968, TMs (Box-folder 12:038)
- CREDIT UNION CORRESPONDENCE 1954 - 1974, TL, TLS (2), TMs (Box-folder 12:039)
- CREDIT UNION QUESTIONNAIRE SURVEY September 1971, TL, TMs (Box-folder 12:040)
- LITERATURE FROM C. U. N. A.INTERNATIONAL, INC. 1970, TL, TLS, TMs (Box-folder 12:041)
  FROM CREDIT UNION FILE
- PAMPHLETS ON THE UVA HOSPITAL EMPLOYEES CREDIT UNION 1967 - 1973, Pamphlets (Box-folder 12:042)
- AN INVESTIGATION OF THE POCKET PAGING COMMUNICATION SYSTEM AT THE UVA HOSPITAL February 1968, TMs (Box-folder 12:043)
- REPORT OF AN INVESTIGATION OF COMPLIANCE WITH TITLE VI OF THE CIVIL RIGHTS ACT ON THE PART OF THE UVA HOSPITAL March 1965 - April 1965, TLS, TMs (Box-folder 13:001)
  FROM CIVIL RIGHTS FILE
- TITLE VI COMPLIANCE REPORT, ON-SITE INSPECTION OF HOSPITALS, NURSING HOMES AND HOMES FOR THE AGED January 16, 1971, Qhestionnaire (Box-folder 13:002)
- GUIDELINES FOR COMPLIANCE OF HOSPITALS WITH TITLE VI OF THE CIVIL RIGHTS ACT OF 1964 1971, TMs (Box-folder 13:003)
- POLICY STATEMENT, TITLE VI, CIVIL RIGHTS ACT OF 1964 1972, TMsS (Box-folder 13:004)
- CIVIL RIGHTS FILE 1965 - 1970, Newsclippings (Box-folder 13:005)
- BUSINESS OFFICE CORRESPONDENCE 1949, 1953, TL, TLS (Box-folder 13:006)
- CONTROLLER'S OFFICE CORRESPONDENCE 1951 - 1978, TL, TLS, TMs (Box-folder 13:007)
- MONTHLY INTERNAL OPERATING REPORTS May 1969, TLS, TMs (Box-folder 13:008)
  FROM CONTROLLER'S OFFICE FILE
- WORKSHEETS WITH COMPUTATIONS OF ATYPICAL COSTS 1978, TL, TMs (Box-folder 13:009)
- COMPARISON OF ACTUAL EXPENDITURES WITH BUDGETED ALLOWANCES 1974 - 1975, TMs (Box-folder 13:010)
- ANALYSIS OF NEED FOR RATE INCREASE October 1968, TMs (Box-folder 13:011)
  FROM RATES FILE
- RATES CORRESPONDENCE 1966 - 1969, TLS (2), TL, TMs, Questionnaires (Box-folder 13:012)
- RATES CORRESPONDENCE 1970 - 1973, TL, TLS (2), TMs (Box-folder 13:013)
- CHARGES FOR DAILY CARE October 1968, TMs (Box-folder 13:014)
- SUMMARIES OF RATES FOR CARE & SERVICE AT UVA HOSPITAL 1970, 1976, 1978, TMs (Box-folder 13:015)
- CHARGES FOR DAILY CARE July 1, 1970, TMs (Box-folder 13:016)
- UVA HOSPITAL SCHEDULE OF RATES FOR ALL ACCOMMODATIONS July 1, 1978, TMs (Box-folder 13:017)
- UVA HOSPITAL SCHEDULE OF RATES FOR ALL ACCOMMODATIONS July 1, 1979, TMs (Box-folder 13:018)
- A SUMMARY OF RATES FOR CARE AND SERVICE AT UVA HOSPITAL July 1, 1980, TMs (Box-folder 13:019)
- MISCELLANEOUS RATE CHARTS FOR UVA HOSPITAL 1973 - 1980, TMs (Box-folder 13:020)
- ROOM RATES FROM OTHER HOSPITALS 1967, TLS, TMs (Box-folder 13:021)
  FROM ROOM RATES FILE
- UVA HOSPITAL SUMMARY OF BUDGET FOR FISCAL YEAR 1969-70 1970, TMs (Box-folder 13:022)
- RATES: MISCELLANEOUS 1967 - 1970, Pamphlets, Leaflets, Newsclippings (Box-folder 13:023)
- CAPITAL OUTLAY CORRESPONDENCE 1957 - 1970, TL, TLS (2), TMs (Box-folder 13:024)
- PROPOSED SIX YEAR CAPITAL OUTLAY PROGRAM FOR PERIOD 7-1-56 TO 6-30-62, TMs (Box-folder 13:025)
  FROM CAPITAL OUTLAY FILE
- PROPOSED 8 YEAR CAPITAL OUTLAY PROGRAM FOR THE PERIOD 7-1-58 TO 6-30-66 1958 - 1960, TMs (Box-folder 13:026)
- CAPITAL OUTLAY STUDY, 1962 - 1968 September 30, 1960, TMs (Box-folder 13:027)
- EQUIPMENT LIST FOR UVA HOSPITAL, CAPITAL OUTLAY, 1964-1966 November 30, 1964, AN, TMs (Box-folder 13:028)
- 1966-68 BIENNIUM CAPITAL OUTLAY PROGRAM SUMMARY November 30, 1964, TMs (Box-folder 13:029)
- 1968 - 1970 CAPITAL OUTLAY REQUESTS August 1967, TLS, TMs (Box-folder 13:030)
- PROPOSED 1970 - 1980 CAPITAL OUTLAY PROJECTIONS October - November 1968, TMs (Box-folder 13:031)
- CAPITAL OUTLAY PROGRAM, 1974 -1976 March 1973, TMs (Box-folder 13:032)
- CAPITAL OUTLAY PROGRAM, 1976 - 1978 March 1973, TMs (Box-folder 13:033)
- CAPITAL OUTLAY EQUIPMENT REQUEST FOR BUDGET ITEM #970 (62-64 BIENNIUM), MEDICAL & LABORATORY EQUIPMENT October 1963, AN, TMs (Box-folder 13:034)
- 1968 - 1970 BIENNIUM CAPITAL OUTLAY PROGRAM SUMMARY December 1966, TL, TMs (Box-folder 13:035)
- CAPITAL OUTLAY PROGRAM, 1978 - 1980 March 1973, TMs (Box-folder 13:036)
- PRELIMINARY SUMMARY, 1968-1970 BIENNIUM CAPITAL OUTLAY REQUESTS August 1967, TLS, TMs (Box-folder 13:037)
- INDIVIDUAL PROJECT REPORT September 26, 1960, TMs (Box-folder 13:038)
  RE: ALTERATIONS & ADDITIONS TO UVA HOSPITAL, PHASE II
- REQUESTS FOR AUTHORITY TO PREPARE CAPITAL OUTLAY PLANS 1963 - 1965, Applications (Box-folder 13:039)
- REQUESTS FOR AUTHORITY TO PREPARE CAPITAL OUTLAY PLANS February 1966, TL, TLS, TMs (Box-folder 13:040)
- REQUEST FOR AUTHORITY TO PREPARE CAPITAL OUTLAY PLANS & CAPITAL OUTLAY EQUIPMENT LIST September 1965, TMs (Box-folder 13:041)
- REQUEST FOR AUTHORITY TO PREPARE CAPITAL OUTLAY PLANS August 1966, TMs, Questionnaire (Box-folder 13:042)
- STATE APPROPRIATIONS FOR CAPITAL OUTLAY PROJECTS 1954-1964, TMs (Box-folder 13:043)
- INDIVIDUAL PROJECT DESCRIPTIONS, BIENNIUM 1966-86 November 30, 1964, TMs, Questionnaires (Box-folder 13:044)
  FROM CAPITAL OUTLAY REQUEST FILE
- INDIVIDUAL PROJECT DESCRIPTIONS, BIENNIUM 1968-70 August 15, 1967, TMs (Box-folder 13:045)
- INDIVIDUAL PROJECT REPORT September 26, 1960, TMs (Box-folder 13:046)
  RE: ALTERATIONS & ADDITIONS TO UVA HOSPITAL, PHASE III
- INDIVIDUAL PROJECT DESCRIPTION November 18, 1964, TMs (Box-folder 13:047)
  RE: RENOVATION OF MEDICAL EDUCATION BUILDING
- INDIVIDUAL PROJECT DESCRIPTION December 9, 1966, TMs, Questionnaire (Box-folder 13:048)
  RE: RENOVATION OF MCKIM HALL
- TEXTS OF TWO SPEECHES BY DR. THOMAS H. HUNTER March 1955, TMs (Box-folder 13:049)
- CAPITAL OUTLAY FOR EQUIPMENT August 5, 1965, TLS, TMs (Box-folder 13:050)
- CAPITAL OUTLAY REQUEST: UVA HOSPITAL April 1955, TMs (Box-folder 13:051)
- UVA CAPITAL OUTLAY REQUESTS, 1956-1962 1956 - 1962, TMs (Box-folder 13:052)
- CAPITAL OUTLAY REQUESTS, UVA HOSPITAL DIVISION FOR PERIOD 1960-68 1960 - 1968, TMs (Box-folder 13:053)
  CAPITAL OUTLAY REQUEST FILE
- CAPITAL OUTLAY PORTION OF 1962 - 64 BUDGET REQUEST 1962 - 1964, TMs (Box-folder 13:054)
- INDIVIDUAL PROJECT DESCRIPTIONS June 20, 1963, TMs (Box-folder 13:055)
- INDIVIDUAL PROJECT DESCRIPTIONS July 1, 1963, TMs, questionnaires (Box-folder 13:056)
- INDIVIDUAL PROJECT DESCRIPTION, BIENNIUM 1966 - 1968 November 18, 1964, TMs, Questionnaires (Box-folder 13:057)
- INDIVIDUAL PROJECT DESCRIPTIONS, BIENNIUM 1968 - 1970 November 18, 1964, TMs (Box-folder 13:058)
- INDIVIDUAL PROJECT DESCRIPTION, BIENNIUM 1968 - 1970 November 30, 1964, TMs, Questionnaire (Box-folder 13:059)
- INDIVIDUAL PROJECT DESCRIPTIONS, BIENNIUM 1968 - 1970 December 9, 1966, TMs, Questionnaire (Box-folder 13:060)
- INDIVIDUAL PROJECT DESCRIPTIONS, BIENNIUM 1972 - 1974 December 9, 1966, TMs, Questionnaire (Box-folder 13:061)
- INDIVIDUAL PROJECT DESCRIPTIONS, BIENNIUM 1970 - 1972 January 30, 1969, TMs, Questionnaires (Box-folder 13:062)
  FROM CAPITAL OUTLAY REQUESTS FILE
- INDIVIDUAL PROJECT DESCRIPTIONS, BIENNIUM 1972 - 1974 January 30, 1969, TMs, Questionnaires (Box-folder 13:063)
- INDIVIDUAL PROJECT DESCRIPTIONS, BIENNIUM 1974 - 1976 January 30, 1969, TMs, Questionnaires (Box-folder 13:064)
- TOTAL CAPITAL OUTLAY REQUEST May 1971, TMs (Box-folder 13:065)
- INDIVIDUAL PROJECT DESCRIPTIONS, BIENNIUM 1974 - 1976 March 6, 1973, TMs, Questionnaires (Box-folder 13:066)
- MISCELLANEOUS CAPITAL OUTLAY REQUEST MATERIAL, TMs, Questionnaire (Box-folder 13:067)
- CORNERSTONE LAYING CORRESPONDENCE 1958 - 1959, ALS, TLS, TL (Box-folder 14:001)
  RE: MULTI-STORY ADDITION TO HOSPITAL
- ITEMS PLACED IN CORNERSTONE, UVA HOSPITAL ADDITION June 12, 1959, TMs (Box-folder 14:002)
- PROGRAMS FOR CORNERSTONE LAYING & MEDICAL ALUMNI DAY June 12, 1959, TMs (Box-folder 14:003)
- MEDICAL EDUCATION BUILDING CORRESPONDENCE June 1964 - 1965, AN, TL, TLS (Box-folder 14:004)
- MEDICAL EDUCATION BUILDING CORRESPONDENCE July - October 1965, TL, TLS (2), Floor Plans (Box-folder 14:005)
- MEDICAL EDUCATION BUILDING CORRESPONDENCE November - December 1965, TL, TLS (2), TMs (Box-folder 14:006)
- MEDICAL EDUCATION BUILDING CORRESPONDENCE January - February 1966, ALS, TLS (2), TL (Box-folder 14:007)
- MEDICAL EDUCATION BUILDING CORRESPONDENCE March - December 1966, TL, TLS (2), TMs (Box-folder 14:008)
- MEDICAL EDUCATION BUILDING CORRESPONDENCE January - May 1967, TL, TLS (2), TMs (Box-folder 14:009)
- MEDICAL EDUCATION BUILDING CORRESPONDENCE June - July 1967, TL, TLS (2), AN (Box-folder 14:010)
- MEDICAL EDUCATION BUILDING CORRESPONDENCE August - October 1967, TL, TLS (2), TMs (Box-folder 14:011)
- MEDICAL EDUCATION BUILDING CORRESPONDENCE November - December 1967, TL, TLS, TMs (Box-folder 14:012)
- MEDICAL EDUCATION BUILDING CORRESPONDENCE January - April 1968, TL, TLS (2), TMs (Box-folder 14:013)
- MEDICAL EDUCATION BUILDING CORRESPONDENCE May - June 1968, TL, TLS (2), AN, TMs (Box-folder 14:014)
- MEDICAL EDUCATION BUILDING CORRESPONDENCE July - August 1968, TL, TLS (2), TMs (Box-folder 14:015)
- MEDICAL EDUCATION BUILDING CORRESPONDENCE September 1968 - 1970, TL, TMs, TLS (2) (Box-folder 14:016)
- MEDICAL CENTER PLANNING COMMITTEE MINUTES 1964, TMs (Box-folder 14:017)
- MEDICAL EDUCATION BUILDING COMMITTEE MINUTES & MEMORANDA 1965, TMs, AMs (Box-folder 14:018)
- MEDICAL EDUCATION BUILDING COMMITTEE MINUTES 1966, AMs, TMs (Box-folder 14:019)
- INDIVIDUAL PROJECT DESCRIPTIONS: MEDICAL EDUCATION BUILDING 1964 - 1965, TMs, Questionnaires (Box-folder 14:020)
- OUTLINE OF TENTATIVE ARCHITECTURAL PROGRAM: MEDICAL EDUCATION BUILDING January 15, 1965, TMs (Box-folder 14:021)
- MEDICAL EDUCATION BUILDING ESTIMATE March 12, 1965, TMs (Box-folder 14:022)
- PROJECT CRITERIA & ESTIMATES FOR THE OVERPASS-BRIDGE FOR THE MEDICAL CENTER May 1965, TMs (Box-folder 14:023)
- REQUEST FOR AUTHORITY TO PREPARE CAPITAL OUTLAY PLANS May 14, 1965, TMs (Box-folder 14:024)
- PROJECT SCHEDULE: MEDICAL EDUCATION BUILDING May 17, 1965, TMs (Box-folder 14:025)
- FLOORPLANS FOR MEDICAL EDUCATION BUILDING June 3, 1965, Blueprints (Box-folder 14:026)
- AVAILABLE PARKING SPACES TO MEDICAL CENTER November 3, 1965, AMs, TMs (Box-folder 14:027)
- SKETCH OF MEDICAL EDUCATION BUILDING December 22, 1965, TLS (2), Floorplan (Box-folder 14:028)
- MATERIAL ON RELATIVE CONSTRUCTION COSTS 1966, TMs (Box-folder 14:029)
  MEDICAL EDUCATION BUILDING FILE
- PRELIMINARY FLOOR PLANS: MEDICAL EDUCATION BUILDING January 11, 1966, TLS, Floorplans (Box-folder 14:030)
- NOTES ON WASHINGTON TRIP-JANUARY 13-14, 1966 January 13, 1966, TMs (Box-folder 14:031)
  FROM MEDICAL EDUCATION BUILDING FILE
- NEW MEDICAL EDUCATION BUILDING February 1966, TMs (Box-folder 14:032)
- PROJECT SCHEDULE & ESTIMATES FOR MEDICAL EDUCATION BUILDING October - November 1966, TMs (Box-folder 14:033)
- OUTLINE OF ARCHITECTURAL PROGRAM: MEDICAL EDUCATION BUILDING November 1966, TL, TMs (Box-folder 14:034)
- GRANT-IN-AID AWARD FOR HEALTH RESEARCH FACILITIES CONSTRUCTION 1966 - 1967, AN, TLS, Questionnaire (Box-folder 14:035)
- DRAFTS OF CONTRACTS WITH ARCHITECTS FOR MEDICAL COMMUNICATIONS BUILDING October 1967, TLS, TMs (Box-folder 14:036)
- U.S. DEPARTMENT OF LABOR QUESTIONNAIRE 1968, Questionnaire (Box-folder 14:037)
  RE: RATES TO BE PAID MEDICAL EDUCATION BUILDING CONSTRUCTION WORKERS
- APPLICATION FOR APPROVAL OF WORKING DRAWINGS AND SPECIFICATIONS March 11, 1968, Application (Box-folder 14:038)
- MEDICAL EDUCATION BUILDING ESTIMATES March - November 1968, TMs (Box-folder 14:039)
- MEMORANDUM OF MEETING APRIL 26, 1968 April 30, 1968, TMs (Box-folder 14:040)
- MEMORANDA OF MEETINGS RE: MEDICAL EDUCATION BUILDING June 19-21, 1968, TMs (Box-folder 14:041)
- LIST OF PROPOSED OMISSIONS OR REDUCTIONS IN THE MEDICAL EDUCATION BUILDING July 1968, TMs (Box-folder 14:042)
- COST SAVING SUGGESTIONS FOR MEDICAL EDUCATION BUILDING, UVA September 1968, TMs (Box-folder 14:043)
- SUMMARY OF ITEMS FOR COST REDUCTION, MEDICAL EDUCATION BUILDING, UVA October 4, 1968, TMs (Box-folder 14:044)
- COST SAVING SUGGESTIONS SUMMARY October 8, 1968, TMs (Box-folder 14:045)
- COST SAVING SUGGESTIONS SUMMARY October - November 1968, TL, TMs (Box-folder 14:046)
- ADDITIONAL ITEMS DEFERRED ON MEDICAL EDUCATION BUILDING October 10, 1968, TMs (Box-folder 14:047)
- COST SAVINGS SUGGESTIONS SUMMARY October 14, 1968, TL, TMs (Box-folder 14:048)
- BUDGET COST REPORT FOR MEDICAL EDUCATION BUILDING AT UVA November 18, 1968, TL, TMs (Box-folder 14:049)
- PRE-BID COST REPORT FOR MEDICAL-EDUCATION BUILDING, UVA January 14, 1964, TMs (Box-folder 14:050)
- APPLICATION FOR APPROVAL OF WORKING DRAWINGS AND SPECIFICATIONS January 22-23, 1969, TL (Box-folder 14:051)
- MEDICAL EDUCATION BUILDING MISCELLANEOUS 1964 - 1968, AMs, Newsclipping (Box-folder 14:052)
- REVISION OF SPACE ALLOCATION PLANS FOR MEDICAL EDUCATION BUILDING November 22, 1965, ANS, TLS, TMs (Box-folder 14:053)
- MATERIALS FOR GAMMA AND X-RAY PROTECTION 1955, Photocopy of Reprinted Article (Box-folder 15:001)
- FLOOR PLANS FROM ALTERATIONS/ADDITIONS FILE, Floor Plans (Box-folder 15:002)
- CONSTRUCTION: AMERICAN STERILIZER COMPANY CORRESPONDENCE 1951 - 1961, TL, TLS (2), TMs (Box-folder 15:003)
- AMERICAN STERILIZER COMPANY EQUIPMENT SUMMARY FOR UVA HOSPITAL July 1954, TMs (Box-folder 15:004)
- ARRANGEMENT OF EQUIPMENT AND FACILITIES IN OPERATING ROOM 1958, Floor Plans (Box-folder 15:005)
- CONSTRUCTION ARCHITECTURAL ADVISORY COMMITTEE CORRESPONDENCE 1954 - 1956, TL, TLS (2) (Box-folder 15:006)
- CONSTRUCTION CORRESPONDENCE 1950, TL, TLS (2) (Box-folder 15:0017)
- CONSTRUCTION: ADDITION TO BARRINGER WING CORRESPONDENCE 1951, TMs, TLS (2), TL, AL (Box-folder 15:008)
- CONSTRUCTION OF BARRINGER WING ADDITION CORRESPONDENCE Jnauary - February 1952, TL, TLS (2) (Box-folder 15:009)
- CONSTRUCTION OF BARRINGER WING ADDITION CORRESPONDENCE March - April 1952, TL, TLS (2) (Box-folder 15:010)
- CONSTRUCTION OF BARRINGER WING ADDITION CORRESPONDENCE May - December 1952, TLS (2), TL, AN, TMs (Box-folder 15:011)
- CONSTRUCTION OF BARRINGER WING ADDITION CORRESPONDENCE January - March 1953, TL, TLS (2) (Box-folder 15:012)
- CONSTRUCTION OF BARRINGER WING ADDITION CORRESPONDENCE April - August 1953, TLS (2), TL, TN (Box-folder 15:013)
- CONSTRUCTION OF BARRINGER WING ADDITION CORRESPONDENCE September - December 1953, TN, TL, TLS (Box-folder 15:014)
- CONSTRUCTION OF BARRINGER WING ADDITION CORRESPONDENCE January - February 1954, TL, TMs, TLS (Box-folder 15:015)
- CONSTRUCTION OF BARRINGER WING ADDITION CORRESPONDENCE March - April 1954, TL, TLS (2) (Box-folder 15:016)
- SUMMARY OF RECOMMENDATIONS FROM ARCHITECTURAL ADVISORY COMMITTEE October 1954, TL, TMs (Box-folder 15:017)
- CONSTRUCTION OF ARCHITECTURAL ADVISORY COMMITTEE MINUTES 1954 - 1956, TMs (Box-folder 15:018)
- CONSTRUCTION OF BARRINGER WING ADDITION CORRESPONDENCE September 21, 1954, TL, TLS (2) (Box-folder 15:019)
- CONSTRUCTION OF BARRINGER WING ADDITION CORRESPONDENCE November - December 1954, TL, TLS (2) (Box-folder 15:020No)
- CONSTRUCTION OF BARRINGER WING ADDITION CORRESPONDENCE 1955, TLS (2), TL (Box-folder 15:021)
- CONSTRUCTION OF BARRINGER WING ADDITION CORRESPONDENCE February - May 1955, TL, TLS (2) (Box-folder 15:022)
- CONSTRUCTION OF BARRINGER WING ADDITION CORRESPONDENCE June 1953 - June 1963, TL, TLS (2) (Box-folder 15:023)
- EXHIBITS: DAVIS-BARRINGER ADDITION September 1951, TMs (Box-folder 15:024)
  RE: PLANS AND ESTIMATES FOR THE NEW WING
- ADDITION TO BARRINGER WING, UNIVERSITY OF VIRGINIA HOSPITAL: SUGGESTIONS MADE BY DIRECTOR'S OFFICE January 19, 1954, TMs, AMs (Box-folder 15:025)
  ARCHITECT'S FINISH SCHEDULE